{
    "subject": "Julie_Clary",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Joseph_Bonaparte",
    "human_readable": "Julie Clary is married to Joseph Bonaparte.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9266571402549744,
            "question": "To whom was Julie Clary married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9258971810340881,
            "question": "Is Julie Clary married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9173939228057861,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Julie Clary and Joseph Bonaparte?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9095873832702637,
            "question": "Who is married to Joseph Bonaparte?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8876858949661255,
            "question": "Is there a connection between Julie Clary and Joseph Bonaparte?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.885970413684845,
            "question": "What can you say about the relationship between Julie Clary and Joseph Bonaparte?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8800139427185059,
            "question": "Who is known for being married to Joseph Bonaparte?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.874904215335846,
            "question": "Name the spouse of Julie Clary."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7631656527519226,
            "question": "Can you provide details about Julie Clary's marriage?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.630694568157196,
            "question": "Who is Joseph Bonaparte?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Julie Clary is married to Joseph Bonaparte.",
            "html": "yago_28993_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you provide details about Julie Clary's marriage?",
            "html": "yago_28993_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Name the spouse of Julie Clary.",
            "html": "yago_28993_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who is known for being married to Joseph Bonaparte?",
            "html": "yago_28993_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28993_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28993_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28993_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28993_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28993_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28993_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28993_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28993_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28993_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28993_70.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the response:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple. The documents mention that Marie Julie Clary was the wife of Joseph Bonaparte, who was King of Naples from 1806 \u2013 1808, and King of Spain from 1808 \u2013 1813."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\n**Explanation:** The provided documents state that Marie-Julie Clary was the wife of Joseph Bonaparte, confirming that Julie Clary is indeed married to Joseph Bonaparte."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}